AoM Publications 5289 PUBS
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series XXVII: Operations Management Division, 1974-2010
  - Perspectives, 1981-1990 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Item 1: Ballot, Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
      By Production/Operations Management Division. Item is in English.
    - Item 2: Ballot, Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Item 3: Ballot, Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Item 4: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
      By Production/Operations Division. Fall 1981. Item is in English.
    - Item 5: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Item 6: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
      By Production/Operations Division. Spring 1982. Item is in English.
    - Item 7: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Item 8: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
      By Production/Operations Division. Fall 1982. Item is in English.
    - Item 9: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Item 10: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Item 11: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
      By Production/Operations Division. Spring 1983. Item is in English.
    - Item 12: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Item 13: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Item 14: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
      By Production/Operations Division. Fall 1984. Item is in English.
    - Item 15: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Item 16: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Item 17: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
      By Production/Operations Division. Spring 1985. Item is in English.
    - Item 18: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Item 19: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Item 20: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Item 21: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
      By Production/Operations Division. Fall 1985. Item is in English.
    - Item 22: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Item 23: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
      By Production/Operations Division. Spring 1986. Item is in English.
    - Item 24: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Item 25: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Item 26: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
      By Production/Operations Division. Fall 1986. Item is in English.
    - Item 27: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Item 28: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
      By Production/Operations Division. Spring 1987. Item is in English.
    - Item 29: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Item 30: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Item 31: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
      By Production/Operations Division. Fall 1987. Item is in English.
    - Item 32: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Item 33: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
      By Production/Operations Division. Spring 1988. Item is in English.
    - Item 34: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Item 35: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
      By Production/Operations Division. Fall 1988. Item is in English.
    - Item 36: Letter to P/OM Associates, Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
      By Vernon M. Buhehler. October 1988. Item is in English.
    - Item 37: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Item 38: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
      By Production/Operations Division. Spring 1989. Item is in English.
    - Item 39: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Item 40: Perspective, Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Item 41: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
      By Production/Operations Division. Fall 1989. Item is in English.
    - Item 42: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Item 43: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Item 44: POM Chronicle, Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
      By Production and Operations Management Society. Fall 1989. Item is in English.
    - Item 45: POM Chronicle, Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Item 46: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Item 47: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
      By Production/Operations Division. Spring 1990. Item is in English.
    - Item 48: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Item 49: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Item 50: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
      By Production/Operations Division. Fall 1990. Item is in English.
    - Item 51: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Item 52: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Perspectives, 1991-2001 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Item 1: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 29)
      By Production/Operations Division. Spring 1991. Item is in English.
    - Item 2: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Item 3: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 29)
      By Production/Operations Division. Fall 1991. Item is in English.
    - Item 4: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Item 5: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Item 6: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 29)
      By Production/Operations Division. Spring 1992. Item is in English.
    - Item 7: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Item 8: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Item 9: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 29)
      By P.O.M. Division. Fall 1992. Item is in English.
    - Item 10: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Item 11: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Item 12: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 29)
      By P.O.M. Division. Spring 1993. Item is in English.
    - Item 13: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Item 14: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Item 15: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 29)
      By P.O.M. Division. Fall 1993. Item is in English.
    - Item 16: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Item 17: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 29)
      By P.O.M. Division. Spring 1994. Item is in English.
    - Item 18: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Item 19: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Item 20: Perspective, Publication (Box 3, Folder 29)
      By P.O.M. Division. Summer 1995. Item is in English.
    - Item 21: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 29)
      By Operations Management Division. Summer 1995. Item is in English.
    - Item 22: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Item 23: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 29)
      By Operations Management Division. Fall 1995. Item is in English.
    - Item 24: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Item 25: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Item 26: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 29)
      By Operations Management Division. Fall 1997. Item is in English.
    - Item 27: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Item 28: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Item 29: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 29)
      By Operations Management Division. Fall 1998. Item is in English.
    - Item 30: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Item 31: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Item 32: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 29)
      By Operations Management Division. Summer 1999. Item is in English.
    - Item 33: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Item 34: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Item 35: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 29)
      By Operations Management Division. Fall 2000. Item is in English.
    - Item 36: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Item 37: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 29)
      By Operations Management Division. Spring 2001. Item is in English.
    - Item 38: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Item 39: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Perspectives, 1993-1998 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Item 1: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 28)
      By Operations Management Division. Fall 1994. Item is in English.
    - Item 2: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Item 3: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Item 4: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 28)
      By P/OM Division. Fall 1993. Item is in English.
    - Item 5: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Item 6: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 28)
      By Operations Management Division. Summer 1998. Item is in English.
    - Item 7: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 28)
      By Operations Mangement Division. Fall 1998. Item is in English.
  - Perspectives, 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Item 1: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 30)
      By Operations Management Division. Spring 2003. Item is in English.
    - Item 2: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Item 3: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Item 4: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 30)
      By Operations Management Division. Spring 2002. Item is in English.
    - Item 5: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Item 6: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Perspectives, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Item 1: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 31)
      By Operations Management Division. Fall 2004. Item is in English.
    - Item 2: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Item 3: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Item 4: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 31)
      By Operations Management Division. Spring 2004. Item is in English.
    - Item 5: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Item 6: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Perspectives, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Item 1: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 32)
      By Operations Management Division. Fall 2005. Item is in English.
    - Item 2: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Item 3: Perspectives, Publication (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Perspectives, 2006 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Perspectives, 2006 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Perspectives, 2007 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Perspectives, 2007 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Perspectives, 2011 (Box 40, Folder 24)
  - Perspectives, 2010 (Box 39, Folder 13)
- Series XXVIII: Organization and Management Theory Division, 1980-2005
  - Organization and Management Theory Division Newsletter, 1974-1997 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Item 1: Proposed Organization Theory Doctoral Consortium, Publication (Box 4, Folder 6)
      By John Slocum. Item is in English.
    - Item 2: OM Division Self-Study Survey and Beyond, Publication (Box 4, Folder 6)
      By James P. Gilbert. January 1997. Item is in English.
    - Item 3: OM Division Self-Study Survey and Beyond, Publication (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Item 4: OM Division Self-Study Survey and Beyond, Publication (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Item 5: Newsletter of the Organization Theory and Management Division, Publication (Box 4, Folder 6)
      By Organization Theory and Management Division. October 1974. Item is in English.
    - Item 6: Organization and Management Theory Division Newsletter, Publication (Box 4, Folder 6)
      By Don Hellriegel. April 1980. Item is in English.
    - Item 7: Organizaion and Management Theory Division, Publication (Box 4, Folder 6)
      By Andrew Van de Van. March 1982. Item is in English.
    - Item 8: Organizatoin and Management Theory Division, Publication (Box 4, Folder 6)
      By Andrew Van de Van. June 1982. Item is in English.
    - Item 9: Organization and Management Theory Division, Publication (Box 4, Folder 6)
      By Andrew Van de Ven. June 1982. Item is in English.
    - Item 10: Organization and Management Theory Division, Publication (Box 4, Folder 6)
      By Andrew Van de Ven. March 1982. Item is in English.
    - Item 11: Organization and Management Theory Division, Publication (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Item 12: Organization and Management Theory Division, Publication (Box 4, Folder 6)
      By Noel M. Tichy. June 1983. Item is in English.
    - Item 13: Organization and Management Theory Division, Publication (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Item 14: Organization and Management Theory Division, Publication (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Item 15: Organization and Management Theory Division, Publication (Box 4, Folder 6)
      By Noel M. Tichy. July 1983. Item is in English.
    - Item 16: Organization and Management Theory Division, Publication (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Item 17: Organization and Management Theory Division, Publication (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Item 18: Organization and Management Theory Division, Publication (Box 4, Folder 6)
      By Bob Miles. March 1984. Item is in English.
    - Item 19: Organization and Management Theory Division, Publication (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Item 20: Organization and Management Theory Division, Publication (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Item 21: Organization and Management Theory Division, Publication (Box 4, Folder 6)
      By Bob Miles. June 1984. Item is in English.
    - Item 22: Organization and Management Theory Division, Publication (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Item 23: Organization and Management Theory Division, Publication (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Item 24: Newsletter of the Organization and Management Theory Division of the Academy of Management, Publication (Box 4, Folder 6)
      By Organization and Management Theory Division. Fall 1984. Item is in English.
    - Item 25: Newsleter of the Organization and Management Theory Division of the Academy of Management, Publication (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Item 26: Newsletter of the Organization and Management Theory Division of the Academy of Management, Publication (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Item 27: Newsletter of the Organization and Management Theory Division of the Academy of Management, Publication (Box 4, Folder 6)
      By Organization and Management Theory Division. Spring 1985. Item is in English.
    - Item 28: Newsletter of the Organization and Management Theory Division of the Academy of Management, Publication (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Item 29: Newsletter of the Organization and Management Theory Division of the Academy of Management, Publication (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Item 30: Newsletter of the Organization and Management Theory Division of the Academy of Management, Publication (Box 4, Folder 6)
      By Organization and Management Theory Division. Summer 1985. Item is in English.
    - Item 31: Newsletter of the Organization and Management Theory Division of the Academy of Management, Publication (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Item 32: Newsleter of the Organization and Management Theory Division of the Academy of Management, Publication (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Item 33: Newsletter of the Organization and Management Theory Division of the Academy of Management, Publication (Box 4, Folder 6)
      By Organization and Management Theory Division. Winter 1985. Item is in English.
    - Item 34: Newsletter of the Organization and Management Theory Division of the Academy of Management, Publication (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Item 35: Organization and Management Theory Division Officer Election, Publication (Box 4, Folder 6)
      By Organization and Management Theory Division. University of Michigan Business School. Item is in English.
    - Item 36: Organization and Management Theory Division Officer Election, Publication (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Item 37: Organization and Management Theory Division Officer Election, Publication (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Organization and Management Theory Division Newsletter, 1986-1988 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Item 1: The Organization and Management Theory Division Newsletter, Publication (Box 4, Folder 7)
      By Organization and Management Theory Division. Spring 1986. Item is in English.
    - Item 2: The Organization and Management Theory Division Newsletter, Publication (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Item 3: The Organization and Management Theory Division Newsletter, Publication (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Item 4: Nomination Form for OMT Officers Election, Publication (Box 4, Folder 7)
      By Organization and Management Theory Division. Item is in English.
    - Item 5: Nomination Form for OMT Officers Election, Publication (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Item 6: Nomination Form for OMT Officers Election, Publication (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Item 7: July 29, 1986, Publication (Box 4, Folder 7)
      By E. Allen Slusher, Allen C. Bluedorn. July 1986. Item is in English.
    - Item 8: The Organization and Management Theory Division Newsletter, Publication (Box 4, Folder 7)
      By Organization and Management Theory Division. Summer 1986. Item is in English.
    - Item 9: The Organization and Management Theory Division Newsletter, Publication (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Item 10: The Organization and Management Theory Division Newsletter, Publication (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Item 11: The Organization and Management Theory Division Newsletter, Publication (Box 4, Folder 7)
      By Organization and Management Theory Division. Fall 1986. Item is in English.
    - Item 12: The Organization and Management Theory Division Newsletter, Publication (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Item 13: The Organization and Management Theory Division Newsletter, Publication (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Item 14: The Organization and Management Theory Division Newsletter, Publication (Box 4, Folder 7)
      By Organization and Management Theory Division. Spring 1987. Item is in English.
    - Item 15: The Organization and Management Theory Division Newsletter, Publication (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Item 16: The Organization and Management Theory Division Newsletter, Publication (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Item 17: The Organization and Management Theory Division Newsletter, Publication (Box 4, Folder 7)
      By Organization and Management Theory Division. Fall 1987. Item is in English.
    - Item 18: The Organization and Management Theory Division Newsletter, Publication (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Item 19: The Organization and Management Theory Division Newsletter, Publication (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Item 20: The Organization and Management Theory Division Newsletter, Publication (Box 4, Folder 7)
      By Organization and Management Theory Division. Winter 1987. Item is in English.
    - Item 21: The Organization and Management Theory Division Newsletter, Publication (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Item 22: The Organization and Management Theory Division Newsletter, Publication (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Item 23: The Organization and Management Theory Division Newsletter, Publication (Box 4, Folder 7)
      By Organization and Management Theory Division. Spring 1988. Item is in English.
    - Item 24: The Organization and Management Theory Division Newsletter, Publication (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Item 25: The Organization and Management Theory Division Newsletter, Publication (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Item 26: The Organization and Management Theory Division Newsletter, Publication (Box 4, Folder 7)
      By Organization and Management Theory Division. Winter 1988. Item is in English.
    - Item 27: The Organization and Management Theory Division Newsletter, Publication (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Item 28: The Organization and Management Theory Division Newsletter, Publication (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - OMT Newsletter, 1988-1992 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Item 1: OMT Newsletter, Publication (Box 4, Folder 8)
      By Organization and Management Theory Division. Fall 1988. Item is in English.
    - Item 2: OMT Newsletter, Publication (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Item 3: OMT Newsletter, Publication (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Item 4: OMT Newsletter, Publication (Box 4, Folder 8)
      By Organization and Management Theory Division. Spring 1989. Item is in English.
    - Item 5: OMT Newsletter, Publication (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Item 6: OMT Newsletter, Publication (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Item 7: OMT Newsletter, Publication (Box 4, Folder 8)
      By Organization and Management Theory Division. Fall 1989. Item is in English.
    - Item 8: OMT Newsletter, Publication (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Item 9: OMT Newsletter, Publication (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Item 10: OMT Newsletter, Publication (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Item 11: OMT Newsletter, Publication (Box 4, Folder 8)
      By Organization and Management Theory Division. Winter 1989. Item is in English.
    - Item 12: OMT Newsletter, Publication (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Item 13: OMT Newsletter, Publication (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Item 14: OMT Newsletter, Publication (Box 4, Folder 8)
      By Organization and Management Theory Division. Spring 1990. Item is in English.
    - Item 15: OMT Newsletter, Publication (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Item 16: OMT Newsletter, Publication (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Item 17: OMT Newsletter, Publication (Box 4, Folder 8)
      By Organization and Management Theory Division. Fall 1990. Item is in English.
    - Item 18: OMT Newsletter, Publication (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Item 19: OMT Newsletter, Publication (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Item 20: OMT Newsletter, Publication (Box 4, Folder 8)
      By Organization and Management Theory Division. Winter 1990. Item is in English.
    - Item 21: OMT Newsletter, Publication (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Item 22: OMT Newsletter, Publication (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Item 23: OMT Newsletter, Publication (Box 4, Folder 8)
      By Organization and Management Theory Division. Spring 1991. Item is in English.
    - Item 24: OMT Newsletter, Publication (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Item 25: OMT Newsletter, Publication (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Item 26: OMT Newsletter, Publication (Box 4, Folder 8)
      By Organization and Management Theory Division. Fall 1991. Item is in English.
    - Item 27: OMT Newsletter, Publication (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Item 28: OMT Newsletter, Publication (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Item 29: OMT Newsletter, Publication (Box 4, Folder 8)
      By Organization and Management Theory Division. Winter 1991. Item is in English.
    - Item 30: OMT Newsletter, Publication (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Item 31: OMT Newsletter, Publication (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Item 32: OMT Newsletter, Publication (Box 4, Folder 8)
      By Organization and Management Theory Division. Spring 1992. Item is in English.
    - Item 33: OMT Newsletter, Publication (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Item 34: OMT Newsletter, Publication (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Item 35: OMT Newsletter, Publication (Box 4, Folder 8)
      By Organization and Management Theory Division. Fall 1992. Item is in English.
    - Item 36: OMT Newsletter, Publication (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Item 37: OMT Newsletter, Publication (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Item 38: OMT Newsletter, Publication (Box 4, Folder 8)
      By Organization and Management Theory Division. Winter 1992. Item is in English.
    - Item 39: OMT Newsletter, Publication (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Item 40: OMT Newsletter, Publication (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - OMT Newsletter, 1993-1997 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Item 1: OMT Newsletter, Publication (Box 4, Folder 9)
      By Organization and Management Theory Division. Spring 1993. Item is in English.
    - Item 2: OMT Newsleter, Publication (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Item 3: OMT Newsletter, Publication (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Item 4: OMT Newsletter, Publication (Box 4, Folder 9)
      By Organization and Management Theory Division. Fall 1993. Item is in English.
    - Item 5: OMT Newsletter, Publication (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Item 6: OMT Newsletter, Publication (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Item 7: OMT Newsletter, Publication (Box 4, Folder 9)
      By Organization and Management Theory Division. Winter 1993. Item is in English.
    - Item 8: OMT Newsletter, Publication (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Item 9: OMT Newsletter, Publication (Box 4, Folder 9)